Man,I sure miss Julie.
我好想念茱莉
Spanish midgets.
西班牙侏儒
Spanish midgets wrestling....
西班牙侏儒摔角…
Julie! Okay,I see how you got there.
茱莉！我明白是怎么想到她的
You ever figure out what that thing's for?
你有想过电话用来做什么吗？
I'm trying this screening thing.
我在过滤电话
If I always answer the phone, people will think I have no life.
我想如果我老是去接的话 大家会以为我没有生活
My God! Rodrigo never gets pinned!
老天啊，罗里哥真是西方不败
At the sound of the beep, you know what to do.
听到哔声后 知道该怎么做吧？
Hello. I'm looking for Bob.
我要找小包
This is Jade.
我是小洁
I don 't know if you 're still at this number,but I was thinking...
我不知道你的电话改了没有 不过我不断在想…
...about how great it was. I know it's been three years...
…我们过去那段美好的时光 我知道都已经三年了啦…
...but I was hoping we could hook up again.
…可是我希望我们能够重修旧好
I barely had the nerve to make this call...
我提不起勇气打电话…
-...so you know what I did? -What?
…你知道我怎么样吗？ 怎么样？
I got a little drunk...
我喝得茫茫的…
...and naked.
…还一丝不挂
Bob here!
我是小包
The One With Five Steaks and An Eggplant
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
六人行 第2季 第05集 五块牛排和一根茄子
So what have you been up to?
你近来都在干什么呢？
Oh,you know,the usual.
跟平常一样啊
Teaching aerobics...
教有气舞蹈…
...partying way too much.
…玩得太疯狂
And in case you wondered...
如果你想知道的话…
... those are my legs on the new James Bond poster.
…新007电影海报上那双腿 是我的
Can you hold on? I have another call.
你请等一下，我有插拨
-I love her! -I know.
我爱她 我知道
-I'm back. -So are we gonna get together?
我回来了 那我们到底要不要聚一聚啊？
Absolutely.
当然要了
How about tomorrow afternoon?
明天下午怎么样？
Do you know Central Perk? Say,five-ish?
你知道格林威治村 中央公园咖啡吗？五点钟左右
Great. I'll see you then.
太棒了，到时候见
Having a phone has finally paid off.
我装上电话，终于物有所值了
You do a good Bob impression...
就算你装小包装得很像…
... but when she sees you tomorrow...
…等到她明天一看到你…
...she's gonna realize you're not Bob.
…就会发现你不是小包了
I'm hoping that when Bob doesn't show up...
我只希望当她知道 小包放她鸽子的时候…
...she'll seek comfort in the arms of the stranger at the next table.
…她会投向邻桌的 陌生人的怀抱
Oh,my God. You are pure evil.
老天，你真是邪恶到家
Okay,pure evil...
邪恶到家…
... horny and alone.
…饥渴兼孤单
I've done this.
这我都试过了
Yeah,everybody's here.
对，大家都在
Hey,everybody! Say hi to Julie in New Mexico!
各位，跟新墨西哥的茱莉 打声招呼吧
Hi,Julie.
茱莉…
While Ross is on the phone...
趁罗斯在讲电话…
...everybody owes me 62 bucks for his birthday.
…每人缴62块庆祝他的生日
Is there any chance that you're rounding up from...
你可不可以将就一下…
...you know...
…譬如说…
...from like 20?
…每个人缴20块就好了
Hey,we got the gift, the concert and the cake.
少来了 要有礼物，演唱会，还有蛋糕
Do we need a cake?
蛋糕需要吗？
I know it's a little steep.
各位，我知道这数目多了一点
But it's Ross.
不过是罗斯的生日呀
It's Ross.
不过是罗斯呀
See you later. I gotta go...
好了，咱们待会儿见 我还得去…
...do a thing!
…做一件事
Okay,sweetheart, I'll call you later.
好了，甜心，我晚上再打给你
You're not going through with this,are you?
你不是真的要那么做吧，老兄
You know,I think I might just.
我非做不可
What are you guys doing for dinner tonight?
你们晚上吃什么？
Well,I gotta start saving up for Ross' birthday.
我想我要开始 为罗斯的生日存钱了
I guess I'll just stay home and eat dust bunnies.
我的菜单是在家里吃西北风
Can you believe how much this costs?
这个可要花很多钱啊
Do you guys ever get the feeling that...
你们有时候会不会觉得…
... Chandler and those guys...
…钱德，他们…
...don't get that we don't make that much money?
…根本不明白 我们赚的钱没他们多
They always say let's go here,let's go there.
他们总是说 “咱们去这儿，去那儿”
Like we can afford to go here and there.
好像我们真的有那个闲钱一样
Yes,and we always have to go to, you know,someplace nice.
而且我们总是得去“好地方” 你知道吗？
And we can't say anything about it, because this is a birthday thing...
我们连反对的权利都没有 因为这是罗斯的生日…
...and it's "for Ross."
…罗斯的
For Ross.
罗斯的…
Oh,my God!
老天
I'm at work...
我在上班…
...just an ordinary day, chop,chop,saute,saute.
…跟平常的一天一样 切切切，煎煎煎
Suddenly,Leon,the manager, calls me into his office.
突然间呢，我们经理李昂 叫我去他的办公室
They fired the lunch chef, and guess who got the job?
原来他们开除了午餐大厨 你们猜谁取代他的职位了？
If it's not you, this is a horrible story.
如果不是你的话 这可是个糟透的故事
Fortunately,it is me.
幸好，那个人是我
And they made me head of purchasing, thank you!
他们还升我为采购主任 感激不尽
That's so cool!
太棒了
Anyway,I think we should go out and celebrate.
我认为我们该出去庆祝一下
You know,someplace nice.
去个好地方
Someplace nice.
How much you think I can get for my kidney?
你们想我的肾能够卖多少钱？
You can't do this.
说真的，你不能够这么做
I can't get a girl like that with conventional methods.
少来了，拘泥于那种传统方法 我永远把不到那种尤物
It doesn't matter.
那有什么关系呢？
She wanted to call Bob. Bob could be who she was meant to be with.
她要找的是小包 小包一定是她理想的对象
You may be destroying their chance for happiness.
你这么做 或许会毁了两个人快乐的机会
We don't know Bob.
我们不认识小包
We know me. We like me. Please let me be happy.
我们认识我，我们喜欢我 拜托，让我快乐起来
Go over there and tell that woman the truth.
你过去告诉那个女人实话
All right.
好啊
Go.
去啊
Listen,I have to....
小姐，我要…
I have to confess something.
我要跟你招认一件事
Yes?
什么事？
Whoever stood you up is a jerk.
放你鸽子的人是混蛋
-How did you -I don't know.
你怎么会… 我不知道
I just had this weird sense. But that's me,I'm weird and sensitive.
我就是有这种怪怪的感应 我就这样，怪怪的又敏感
Tissue?
面纸？
Thanks.
谢谢
No,you keep the pack.
不用，你整包留着吧
I'm all cried out today.
我今天已经“哭”干了
Here is to my sister, the newly appointed head lunch chef.
我敬我刚刚被升为 午餐大厨的老妹一杯
Also in charge of purchasing.
而且她还接掌了采买大权
Head lunch chef, also in charge of purchasing
恭贺她升为午餐大厨 并且接掌采买大权…
Who has her own little desk when Roland's not there.
罗不在的时候 她有自己的小办公桌
Lunch chef,purchasing,own little desk when Roland's not there...
午餐大厨，采购，罗不在时 有自己的小办公桌
-... here's to my -Wait! And I got a beeper!
咱们敬我的老妹… 等等…我还有传呼器
That's fine,I'll just wait.
没关系，我等好了
Sorry.
抱歉…
Monica!
敬摩妮卡
Are we ready to order?
各位可以点菜了吗？
We haven't even looked yet.
对不起，我们还没看菜单
When you do,let me know.
那你们看过之后再叫我
I'll be over there on the edge of my seat.
我会在那边引颈企盼的
Look at these prices!
你们看看这上面的价钱
Yeah,these are pretty "cha-ching."
是呀，都是什么鸡的
I know! What are these, famous chickens?
这什么？名牌鸡吗？
Sorry I'm late. Congratulations,Mon.
抱歉，我迟到了 摩妮卡，恭喜你
I'm not sorry I'm late. How incredible was my afternoon with Jade?
我不后悔我迟到，我跟小洁的 午后约会太不可思议了
Pretty incredible,according to the message on my machine.
根据她在我答录机上 留给你的话的确很不可思议
Why is this woman leaving a message for you on my machine?
钱德，这个女人为什么 会在我的答录机留话给你呢？
I told her that my number was yours...
我必须要告诉她 我的号码是你的号码…
... because I couldn't tell her it was mine...
…因为我不能告诉她 我的号码是我的号码…
... because she thinks my number is Bob's number.
…因为她以为 我的号码是小包的号码
Tell me again. What do I do when Mr. Roper calls?
你再告诉我一次 罗先生打来的时候我怎么办？
Do I dare ask?
可以点菜了吗？
I'll start with the carpaccio, and then the grilled prawns.
好，我要先来一份生牛肉 然后再来一份烤虾
Great,same for me.
听起来不错，我也一样
And for the gentleman?
那这位先生呢？
I'll have the Thai chicken pizza.
我要泰国鸡肉披萨
But if I get it without the nuts and leeks and stuff...
如果我的披萨少加干果，大蒜…
...is it cheaper?
…会不会比较便宜啊？
You'd think,wouldn't you?
你是那么想吗？
I will have the side salad.
好了，我想要点…伴碟沙拉
And what would that be on the side of?
那要伴在什么菜旁边呢？
I don't know.
我不知道
Just put it right here next to my water.
你就帮我放在我的水旁边好了
And for you?
那你呢？
I'm gonna have a cup of the cucumber soup and...
我想我要来一碗黄瓜汤…
...take care.
…保重了
I will have the Cajun catfish.
我要一份纽奥良鲶鱼
Anything else?
就这样吗？
Yes,how about a verse of "Killing Me Softly"?
还有一首“情歌迷死人” 怎么样？
You're gonna sneeze in my fish,aren't you?
你会朝我的鱼打喷嚏 对不对？
Plus tip,divided by six....
加上小费再除以六…
Everyone owes 28 bucks.
好了，每个人给我28块钱
Everyone?
每个人？
Oh! You're right,I'm sorry.
你说得对，对不起
Thank you.
谢谢
It's Monica's big night. She shouldn't pay.
今天是摩妮卡的大日子 她不需要付啊
So five of us is...
用五个人去除…
...33. 50 a piece.
…每个人33.5元
No. No way. Sorry,not gonna happen.
不行，抱歉 那是不可能的事
Prom night flashback.
毕业舞会重演
Sorry,Monica. I'm happy you got promoted...
对不起，摩妮卡 你升了职我替你高兴…
... but cold cucumber mush for 30-something bucks?
…可是冷黄瓜糊要三十几块？
No!
不行
Rachel just had that little salad...
瑞秋只点了那盘小沙拉…
...and Joey with his teeny pizza!
…乔伊只吃了那片小披萨
Okay,Pheebs.
好吧，菲比
How about we'll each pay for what we had?
那我们就各付各的，好吗？
It's no big deal.
小事一桩嘛
Not for you.
对你来讲就是
All right,what's going on?
到底怎么了？
I don't wanna get into this right now.
算了，各位 我现在真的不想谈这个
It'll make everybody uncomfortable.
我觉得 这样只会让大家心里有疙瘩
You can tell us.
拜托，说出来吧
Yeah,hello? It's us. We'll be fine.
对啊，是我们，没关系的
We three...
我们三个…
...feel like that...
…觉得…
...sometimes you guys don't get that....
…你们有时候不太明白…
We don't have as much money as you.
我们没你们那么有钱
I hear you.
我懂了
We can talk about that.
那我们可以谈啊
Well,then...
那么…
...Iet's.
…我们就
I guess I just never think of money as an issue.
我猜我只是 从没想过钱是个问题
-Because you have it. -Good point!
那是因为你有钱 你说得好
So how come you guys haven't talked about this before?
你们以前为何提出来讨论呢？
Because it's always something. Like with Monica's new job...
因为总是有特别的事情 像摩妮卡的新工作…
...or the whole Ross' birthday hoopla.
…或是罗斯的什么啦…
I don't want my birthday to be the source of any kind of negative....
我可不希望我的生日 造成任何的不愉快…
There's gonna be a hoopla?
你们要为我搞什么吗？
Basically there's the thing, and then the stuff after the thing
基本上有这件事啦 然后又是那件事…
If it makes anybody feel better, forget the thing...
如果大家觉得好过一点的话 我们可以忘了那件事…
...and we'll just do the gift.
…只送礼物就好了
Gift? The thing's not the gift?
礼物？礼物不就是那件事吗？
No,we were gonna go see Hootie and the Blowfish.
不，那件事就是我们要去看 “混混与自大狂”
Hootie and the
“混混与自大狂”…
I can catch them on the radio.
我可以听收音机就好了
No. Now I feel bad. You wanna go to the concert.
不，现在我愧疚了 你想去听那场演唱会的？
No,look. It's my birthday...
不，听着，那是我的生日…
...and the important thing is that we're all together.
…最重要的 是我们大家一起过
-All of us. -Together.
全部 一起过
Not at the concert.
不是去演唱会
Thank you.
谢谢
So,the Ebola virus. That's gotta suck,huh?
那个依波拉病毒… 得到一定很惨
Gee,Monica. What's in the bag?
摩妮卡，袋子里有什么？
I don't know,Chandler. Let's take a look.
不知道，钱德 咱们看一下吧
Oh,it's like a skit.
像在演短剧
Why,it's dinner for six. Five steaks...
是六个人的晚餐 五块牛排…
...and an eggplant for Phoebe.
…跟菲比的茄子
We switched suppliers at work,and they gave me the steaks as a thank-you.
我们餐厅换了肉食供应商 新供应商送了我这些牛排谢我
But wait,there's more. Chandler,what is in that envelope?
等等，还有啊… 钱德，那信封里头还有什么？
By the way,this didn't seem so dorky out in the hall.
对了，刚才在外面排演 那没么驴的
Why,it's six tickets to Hootie and the Blowfish!
是六张去看 “混混与自大狂”的票
The Blowfish!
是“自大狂”呀
It's on us. So don't worry. This is...
是我们付钱的，所以别担心 我们…
...our treat.
…请客
Thank you.
谢了
Could you be less enthused?
你们能不能更不起劲儿啊
Look,it's a nice gesture. It is.
各位，你们一番好意
But it just feels like....
可是我们觉得这像…
Like?
像…
Charity.
施舍
Charity?
施舍？
We're just trying to do a nice thing here.
我们只是想让大家高兴
But you have to understand,your "nice thing" makes us feel about this big.
对，罗斯但是你这么做 让我们觉得我们很渺小
Actually,it makes us feel that big.
事实上，我们是这么小
I don't understand. We can't win with you guys.
我不懂 我是说，我们怎样做都不对
If you guys feel this big, maybe that's not our fault.
若你们觉得那么渺小的话 那或许不是我们的错
Maybe that's just how you feel.
或许…那只是你们的感觉
Now you're telling us how we feel.
你要告诉我们有什么感受
We never should have talked about this.
你看嘛，我们根本就不该提的
I'm gonna pass on the concert.
我想我不去演唱会了
I'm just not in a very "Hootie" place right now.
因为我现在 不太有心情去“混”
-Me neither. -Me too.
我也是 我也是
Guys,we bought the tickets.
各位，我们票都已经买好了
Then you'll have extra seats for all your tiaras and stuff.
那你们就有座位 可以放头冠啊什么的
Why did you look at me when you said that?
你说的时候干嘛瞪着我看？
So I guess now we can't go.
这下子我们都不能去了
Do what you want. Do we always have to do everything together?
你们去做你们要做的事啊 我们非得集体行动不可吗？
You know what? You're right.
知道吗？你说得对耶
Fine.
很好
All right.
好吧
We're gonna go.
我们就去
It's not for another six hours. We're gonna go then.
不过还有六个小时 我们到时候再去
Are you ready?
天啊，你准备好了吗？
Just let me grab my jacket and tell you I had sex today.
好了，等我先拿个外套 还有我今天上床了
What? You had sex today?
什么？你今天上床了？
It sounds even cooler when somebody else says it!
从别人嘴里说出来更酷耶
I was awesome. She was biting her lip to stop from screaming.
我棒透了，我害得她必须要 咬住嘴唇忍住尖叫
I know it's been a while, but I took that as a good sign.
我知道我很久没有这样了 但我认为那是个好现象
Still doing the screening?
你还在过滤电话吗？
I had sex today.
我今天上床了
I never have to answer that phone again.
我再也不用去接那个电话
At the sound of the beep, you know what to do.
哔一声过后，你知道怎么做
Hey,Bob. It's Jade.
小包，我是小洁，听着
I wanted to tell you I was really hurt when you didn 't show up yesterday.
你那天放我鸽子 我心里难过极了
And just so you know, I ended up meeting a guy.
结果你知道吗？ 我认识了另一个人
Bob here.
我是小包
So you met someone,huh?
你认识了别人？
Yes,I did.
没错
In fact,I had sex with him two hours ago.
事实上 我两小时前跟他上床了
So how was he?
他怎么样呢？
Oh,Bob,he was nothing compared to you.
小包，跟你比他算什么
I bit my lip to keep from screaming your name.
我得咬住嘴唇 才能不叫出你的名字
Well,that makes me feel so good.
很高兴听你这么讲
It was just so awkward and bumpy.
我是觉得他好没技巧
Maybe he had some kind of new style that you're not familiar with.
或许是因为他采取了一些 你不熟悉的新的酷姿势
You have to get used to it.
你应该要习惯他的做法呀
There wasn 't much time to get used to it...
根本没多少时间可以让我习惯…
...if you know what I mean.
…懂我的意思吗？
You know what? I'm not gonna be able to enjoy this.
知道吗？ 我想我根本没有心情听这个
I know. It's my birthday. We all should be here.
我知道，这是我的生日 我们应该全部在一起的
So let's go.
那么走吧
Well,maybe we should stay for one song.
或许我们应该听一首再走
It would be rude to them for us to leave now.
对呀，反正现在离开 对他们有点不敬
The guys are probably having a great time.
说不定 他们现在正玩得很开心呢
Come on,you guys. One more time.
来吧，再来一次嘛
One.
―
-Amazing! -Excellent!
不可思议 棒透了
I can't believe the guys missed it!
真不能相信他们错过这个
What guys? Oh,yeah.
你说谁？对了
Excuse me. Aren't you Monica Geller?
请问，你是盖勒摩妮卡，对吧？
-Do I know you? -You were my baby-sitter!
我认识你吗？ 你以前当过我的褓姆呀
Oh,my God! Little Stevie Fisher?
天啊，我的小费史提
How have you been?
近来好不好啊？
Good. I'm a lawyer now.
很好，我现在是律师了
You can't be a lawyer. You're 8.
你不可能是律师，你才八岁
It was nice to see you. I gotta run backstage.
听着，很高兴见到你 我要去后台了
Wait,backstage?
等等，后台？
My firm represents the band.
他们是我公司代理的
You guys wanna meet the group?
你们想认识他们吗？
Come on.
那走吧
Are you one of the ones that fooled around with my Dad?
对了 你以前也有跟我爸乱搞吗？
Hey,you guys!
各位
Happy birthday!
生日快乐
Oh,thank you.
谢谢
How was your night last night?
你们昨天晚上过得怎么样？
Oh,well,it pretty much sucked. How was yours?
昨晚真是烂得可以了 你们呢？
Ours pretty much sucked too.
我们也是烂得可以啊
But I ran into Stevie Fisher. Remember him?
但是我碰到了小费史提 你记得吗？
Oh,yeah! I used to baby-sit him.
记得，我以前当过他的褓姆
Hey,how's his dad?
他爸好吗？
Good.
很好
Aside from that,the evening was pretty much a bust.
除此之外 我们昨天整个晚上都满凄惨的
Yeah,we really missed you guys.
对，我们很想念你们
Yeah,we were just saying, this whole thing is so stupid.
对呀，我们刚才还说 这件事太愚蠢了
We just have to really,really not let stuff like money,get like
我们必须真的真的 不让钱这种事情介入…
Is that a hickey?
那是个吻痕吗？
Oh,no,I just....
不，我只是…
I fell down.
我跌倒了
On someone's lips?
跌在别人嘴上？
Where'd you get the hickey?
你那吻痕哪儿来的？
You know,a party or
你知道，派对啊…
What party?
什么派对？
It wasn't a party so much as a...
那不算是派对…
...a gathering of people.
…只能说是一群人聚在一起
With food and music and...
有吃的，有音乐，还有…
...and the band.
…乐团
You partied with Hootie and the Blowfish?
你们跟“混混与自大狂”混？
Yes. Apparently,Stevie and Hootie are like this.
对，很显然史提跟混混是死党
Who gave you that hickey?
那吻痕是谁给的？
That would be the work of a Blowfish.
是其中一个自大狂弄的
I can't believe it! I can't believe this!
我真不敢相信
We're just sitting at home, trying to guess Joey's fingers...
我们只是坐在家里头 猜乔伊的手指头…
...and you're partying and having fun and all:
而你们却跑出去疯狂作乐说：
"Hey,Blowfish,suck on my neck!"
“自大狂吸我脖子”
Don't blame us. You could've been there.
不要怪我们 本来你们也可以去的
What? As part of your "poor friends outreach program"?
什么？当被你们施舍的 穷朋友，是不是？
Oh,great. It's work.
帅，是公司
I don't know what to say. I'm sorry we make more than you.
我不晓得该说什么 很抱歉我们赚的钱比你们多
But we're not gonna feel guilty. We work really hard.
可是我们不想因此有罪恶感 我们很努力的赚钱啊
And we don't work hard?
我们就不努力？
It's Monica. I got a page.
我是摩妮卡 刚刚有人CALL我
It's just that sometimes we like to do stuff that costs a little more.
有时候我们会想做 比较花钱的事情嘛
And you feel like we hold you back.
是我们拖住你了
Leon,wait.
等等
Guys!
各位！
I don't understand.
我不明白
The steaks were a gift from the meat vendor.
那些牛排只是肉商送来的礼物
That was not a kickback.
可不是回扣啊
I'll just replace them, and we can forget the whole thing.
那我买回去还他们 我们把这件事忘掉好了
What corporate policy?
什么公司政策啊？
I just got fired.
我被开除了
Here's your check. That'll be $4. 1 2.
你们的帐单，一共四块两毛
Let me get that.
我来付
You got 5 bucks?
你有没有五块啊？
Here comes the beep. You know what to do.
哔一声过后，你知道怎么做
Hi,it's me.
是我
Listen,Bob. I'm probably way out of line here.
小包 也许我不该做这样的要求
It's been three years,and you 're probably seeing someone else now...
我是说都过三年了 说不定你另外有女朋友了…
...but if we could have one night together,for old time 's sake....
…我们如果能在一起一个晚上 看在往日的份上…
One hot,steamy,wild night....
干柴烈火的一晚…